ZEESHAN HAIDER

Specialist Web & Frontend Developer



0333-4867615 | as8759111@gmail.com | Pakistan, jhelum

ABOUT ME

I'm Zeeshan Haider, a passionate WordPress Developer, Frontend Developer, and Graphic Designer with 2-3 years of hands-on experience. I specialize in creating modern, responsive, and user-friendly websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and WordPress. Alongside development,

EXPERIENCE

2022

FREELANCE WORDPRESS & FRONTEND DEVELOPER | FIVERR | 2022 - PRESENT

- Developed and customized 50+ WordPress websites for clients across various industries.
- Designed modern, responsive layouts using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Integrated WooCommerce for online stores and optimized websites for faster load times.

2023 - 2024

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (PROJECT-BASED) | SELF-EMPLOYED | 2023 - 2024

- Built landing pages, portfolio sites, and eCommerce store interfaces using HTML, CSS. and JS.
- Ensured mobile responsiveness and user-friendly design for better engagement.

EDUCATION

INTERMEDIATE (2ND YEAR) Government College Sohawa – 2024

Diplomas & Certifications

• Diploma in WordPress Development Diploma in Microsoft Excel & Word -

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6+)
- Responsive & Mobile-Friendly Design
- Cross-Browser Compatibility
- Theme Customization & Elementor
- WooCommerce Store Setup
- Plugin Integration & Optimization